既然我们已经完成了对应用程序UI的实现，
Now that we've finished build the UI for our app,
现在需要考虑当应用不在前台的时候，
it's time to think about how it should operate when it's
该如何运行。安卓最厉害的一点就是
not in the foreground. One of the most powerful features of
它能让任何app在后台运行。
Android, is the ability for any app to run in the
但责任越大能力就越大。所以你需要
background. But with great power comes great responsibility. So, you need
非常重视它对资源的消耗。在这门
to be very conscious of how it's consuming resources. In this
课程里，你将会学习安卓框架是如何管理后台程序的
lesson, you'll learn more about how the Android framework manages background
然后你会学到service类，它会帮你实现后台程序的功能
apps and you'll be introduced to the service class to help
实现它。你也会学到通过同步适配器
make that happen. You'll also learn techniques for efficient
和谷歌云消息来进行有效的数据转换。以及
data transfers using sync adapters and Google Cloud messaging. And
学习当你的app没有运行在前台的时候，
be introduced to the notification framework to send messages
notification框架如何发送信息给你的app用户。
to your users when your app isn't in the foreground.